fish.wa.gov.au 2019-06-04

# Privacy

This website privacy statement applies to http://www.fish.wa.gov.au administered by the Department of Fisheries, Western Australia. When you follow a link from this website to another site, we recommend you read and consider the privacy statement of that site.

### Collection of personal information

You can browse the general content of http://www.fish.wa.gov.au anonymously, without disclosing your personal information. However, some of the functionality of the site may require you to provide personal information. Examples of this include where you wish to make an enquiry. We may need to collect, use or disclose personal information to allow us to answer your enquiry or process your transaction.

### Use and disclosure of personal information

Any personal information we collect through http://www.fish.wa.gov.au may be used or disclosed for the primary purpose for which it was collected. We will only use that information to communicate with you in the way indicated.

In some limited circumstances we may also need to use or disclose personal information for other specific purposes, for example where required to do so by law, such as pursuant to the _Freedom of Information Act 1992_ or in response to a subpoena.

### Collection and use of site visit data

The following information may be automatically recorded by this site’s web server for statistical and system administration purposes only:

  * Your server address;

  * Your top level domain name (e.g. .com, .au, .gov);

  * The date and time of your visit to the site;

  * The pages you accessed and downloaded;

  * The address of the last site you visited;

  * Your operating system;

  * The type of browser you are using.

We will not attempt to identify individuals from the above information unless that is necessary to investigate a breach of law or regulation.

### Cookies and web scripts

A cookie is a block of data that is shared between a web server and a user’s browser. Cookies, and the information collected through them, are used by the Department of Fisheries to make this website more efficient. Cookies may be turned off within your browser, however, this may make some functionality of the website unusable.

Pages on this site may be coded with scripts from Google Analytics. This is transparent to the user, as the software makes use of an invisible image at the bottom of the web page. This software stores a cookie in your browser, which contains a unique identifier and sends information to Google Analytics. This enables Google Analytics to track the number of unique visitors to this site. In no way does this unique identifier identify a user personally.

**Last modified:** 8/05/2012 9:59 AM
